bookit.com 2017-06-07

# Privacy Policy | BookIt.com | Powered by FROM™ Technology

For our guests, privacy is of the utmost concern. With the rise in identity theft and fraudulent use of financial information, BookIt.com has made sure that your privacy and the information collected from you is guarded and secured with the most secure technologies.

The Privacy Policy covers treatment of personally identifiable information collected on the BookIt.com website.

BookIt.com collects personally identifiable information in order to process reservations. We ask for your name, email address, street address, zip code, and, (when processing a reservation only) your credit card number. BookIt.com also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP Address and the page you requested, along with requests for specific price quotes for lodging. BookIt.com uses information for these general purposes: to fulfill your requests for reservations or information and to contact you about specials and new products, as well as to determine what offerings are of most interest to our users.

Information from Other Sources

We may receive information about you from other sources such as address information.  This information may help us to improve our ability to serve your needs such as ensuring the accurate delivery of direct mail materials. 

Information Sharing and Disclosure

BookIt.com will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. We need to send the information to companies who work as partners with BookIt.com to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.). This information is limited to only necessary information in reference to any reservations you may make online. Credit Card numbers are never emailed, but are only accessible to our partners who log into a password protected secure site. All such credit card views are logged by BookIt.com as a final protection to our guests. Usually, only top-level personnel at a company are privileged to have access to credit card numbers.

Some of the advertisements and other services that appear on our web site(s) are delivered to you by Internet advertising companies. These companies utilize certain technologies including cookies to deliver advertisements and marketing messages and to collect anonymous information about your visit to our sites and other web sites. If you would like more information about this practice or to opt out of having this information used by companies that are part of the Network Advertising Initiative to provide targeted ads, please visit [//www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)

Display Advertising

BookIt.com utilizes Display Advertising features that may include and are not limited to: Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration, or Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. You can opt-out and manage your settings or customize your Google Display Network ads by going to [//www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads)

Cookies

BookIt.com may set and access cookies on your computer. Web cookies are identifiers which let a Web server know that you are the same person that accessed the server the last time you accessed it. This makes an extended interaction possible.

Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences

BookIt.com gives you the ability to edit your Account Information and preferences at any time.

Security

Your BookIt.com Account Information is password-protected for your privacy and security. In certain areas BookIt.com uses industry-standard 128 bit SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

BookIt.com may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.

Questions or Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions, please [click here to contact us](https://bookit.com/customer-support/).

©2017 BookIt.com

Privacy Policy above is for all BookIt.com generated sites.
